CONTACT

908-370-6530

github.com/MaxFrank13

maxfrank13@gmail.com

www.franklymaxwell.com

linkedin.com/in/maxwell-frank/

MAXWELL FRANK

Frontend Web Developer

Lifetime creator with a background in woodworking and restaurant industries recently making a transition into Web Development. By calling on this personal experience, I provide a unique perspective on the construction of web pages and applications. I find the logistical challenges that programming presents to be a motivating force in my experience as a developer.

SKILLS

- GIT
- HTML/CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- JQUERY
- BOOTSTRAP
- BULMA
- THREEJS
- NODE

ATTRIBUTES

- MOTIVATED
- PERSONABLE
- LEARNER
- LEADER
- PROBLEM SOLVER
- ANIMATED

EDUCATION

University of New Hampshire

Sociology 2015

UNH Coding Bootcamp 2022

Summit High School

2007-2011

Senior Student Humanities Award
Wheeler Family Bowling Scholarship

EXPERIENCE

Falafel Mafia, Portland ME - Cook/Assistant Manager - 2019 – 2021

Cooking to order in a fast-paced environment. Working on food truck and experience with mobile food services.

Hanson Woodturning, Kennebunkport ME - Furniture Craftsman - 2017-2019

Use of milling machines and experience turning raw material into high end finished product. Attention to fine details.

Richardson Allen, Biddeford ME - Woodworker - 2016

Experience with packing and shipping off final product. Use of sprayer to apply marine quality paint.

PROJECTS

CarryOn

Use of OpenTripMap and Unsplash APIs to provide users with a method for finding features to visit while on vacation. Technologies used: HTML/CSS, jQuery, Bulma, Fetch API

Electric Slide

Simple platformer game with vibrant animations. Technologies used: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Canvas API

Weather Dashboard

A weather dashboard for viewing upcoming forecasts of selected locations. Technologies used: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, OpenWeather API, Clay.css

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Distance skateboarding

Hiking & the outdoors

Video games & design